leeco.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy | LeEco

Le Technology, Inc. and its Affiliates, which are referred to collectively as "LeEco", "we" or "us" in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"), know that you care how information about you is used. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Affiliate" means the group of entities which are controlling, controlled by or under common control with Le Technology, Inc., and "control" means possessing, directly or indirectly, the power to direct or cause the direction of the management, policies or operations of an entity, whether through ownership of voting securities, by contract or otherwise. This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what information is collected when you visit our websites or use our products and services, including mobile phones, televisions, TV Boxes, accessories, websites, and software, including mobile applications (each, a "LeEco Service", and collectively, "LeEco Services") and how this information is used, disclosed, transferred, and stored. Some LeEco Services shall provide and be subject to a different privacy policy and in such cases, the terms of the applicable LeEco Service privacy policy will supersede this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies to you if (1) you are located in the United States and use any LeEco Service or (2) if you are located anywhere in the world and visit our websites including leeco.com or any of our other websites or LeEco Services based in or hosted from the United States. If you are located outside of the United States and have purchased, visited, or used any LeEco Service, you should consult the applicable LeEco Service privacy policy for your territory for other terms that may apply to you with respect to LeEco Services you receive outside the United States. Before using or submitting information through any LeEco Service, please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting or using any LeEco Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy and any changes LeEco may make to it and consent to having your information transferred to and/or processed as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the LeEco Services.

 **By visiting our websites or using the LeEco Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, including the arbitration agreement and class action waiver described below.**

**1\. Information We Collects**

We collect information to personalize your experience of the LeEco Services and to provide and improve our services and products. The following are the types of information we collect:

  1. **Information that you provide to LeEco.**
    * We collect information you enter in your use of LeEco Services or give us, our Affiliates or business partners. For example, when you create an account or a profile on a LeEco Service, or sign up for a subscription, we will ask you for  information such as your name, birthdate, address, phone number, email address, password and other relevant  information. When you order a product or paid service from LeEco, we may ask for your name, contact information,  shipping and billing address(es), and payment card information in order to process your orders and provide you with the products and services you requested. When you communicate with others, ask questions or make comments through LeEco Services or when you synchronize data (e.g. photos, contact lists, other materials or data) through the  LeCloud service, we may transmit or store the information on our systems. We also collect the information you  provide to us when you contact us via email, phone, or social media.
    * When you participate in our online sale promotions or surveys, we may ask you for information such as your phone number, email address, occupation, and other information relevant to the promotion survey.
  2. **Third-party Services.** We collect some information from third-party services (e.g., social media services) when you use your credentials for these services to log into a LeEco Service or otherwise link your LeEco account with the third-party service.
  3. **Information we obtain from your use of LeEco Services.** We collect information about how you use LeEco Services, when  you visit our websites, use our software, or interact with our devices. The information we collect about your use of LeEco Services is in a form that does not personally identify you unless we obtain your consent. This information includes:
    * _Device and user activity information. We may collect:_
      * Device information such as IMEI number, device ID and other unique device identifiers, MAC address, device operating system, Internet protocol (IP) addresses; system and performance information; and settings of the device you use to access LeEco Services.
      * Details of how you use LeEco Services, such as the apps you use or the search query terms you enter.
      * Log information, such as the time and duration of your use of the LeEco Services, devices events such as crash events, log files, hardware settings, and source and referral URLs.
    * _Location-based data._ When you use LeEco Services, we may collect information about your location by, for example, using information about your device, including GPS information, Wi-Fi signals, IP address or other unique identifiers. This location data may be used by LeEco and our partners to provide and improve location-based products and services, including advertising and other personalized content.
    * _Cookies and similar technologies._ "Cookies" are small files sent to your device when you visit a website. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be accessed every time you use the LeEco Services. When you use a LeEco Service, we may use session and persistent cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to record information about how you use the LeEco Service, such as geographic and language preferences, the effectiveness of ads, or the content query that directed you to a particular page. We may use cookies in conjunction with advertising to provide you with personalized content. Most browsers allow you to delete cookies and not accept new ones. However, disabling them may prevent you from using certain features or functionality available in LeEco Services.
    * _Video data._ When you activate your use of video within a LeEco Service, you consent to our collection of information regarding the videos accessed. If you wish to withdraw your consent, please disable use of the video-related LeEco service through your device's system settings. If you do so, however, some of the LeEco Services may not function correctly if the video-related LeEco services are disabled.
    * LeEco also may collect other information about you, your devices, or your use of LeEco Services in ways that we describe to you at the point of collection or otherwise with your consent. We may also de-identify or aggregate information collected through the LeEco Services. 

**2\. How We Use Information We Collect**

We use the information we collect to allow us to efficiently process your transactions; to provide, maintain, protect, and improve LeEco Services; and to develop new services and products. We may use information we collect across all LeEco Services you use. We may also use this information to personalize LeEco Services and to help us deliver personalized services, content, and advertising of interest to you. For example, we may use your information to send you communications and respond to your requests, to make it easier for you to share information and content (such as content uploaded through social media), to verify your age or identity, and for security, error reporting, service restriction, loss prevention, and anti-fraud purposes, and to help us to create, to develop, to operate, to deliver and to improve our products, services, content and advertising. We may also use information we collect for internal purposes such as auditing, analysis of your online activities over time, and research to improve the LeEco Services and customer communications.

We also collect information in a form that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual, including de-identified or aggregated information collected regarding customer activities on the LeEco Services. We may collect, use, transfer, store and disclose this non-personal information for any purpose. We treat information collected by cookies as non-personal information as long as it can't be used to identify a particular individual. If we combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information under this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Disclosures to Third Parties**

At times, LeEco may share information with our Affiliates, partners, or vendors that help us provide LeEco Services, including to process payments, analyze data, provide customer service, and help LeEco market and advertise to you. These third parties may be located anywhere in the world, including outside of your country of residence.We also may work with partners to help us deliver LeEco ads to you on third-party websites, applications, or devices. We may share information we collect from you with these partners. To deliver these ads, our partners may collect information about you, your devices, and your use of LeEco Services. This information may include information about your visits to websites and use of applications provided by LeEco and others, your IP address, your Internet service provider, and the browser that you use to visit our websites.

We may be required by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from international, national, federal, state, public, and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence to disclose information. We may also disclose information we collect if we determine that for purposes of national security, public safety, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions, this Privacy Policy, or our other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of LeEco, the LeEco Services, our partners, users, or the public. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, stock sale, merger, sale or divestiture of all or any part of our business, operations or assets, change of control, financing, bankruptcy, or liquidation, we may transfer or disclose information to a third party in connection with those events.

We may also share or disclose de-identified or aggregated information that does not identify specific individuals with our service providers or other third parties for any purpose.

**4\. Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If a child has provided us with personal information, a parent or guardian of that child may send an email message to [Privacy-US@le.com](mailto:privacy-us@le.com?subject=Request%20for%20Child%20Information%20Removal) with "Request for Child Information Removal" on the subject line and information sufficient for us to remove information about the child in the body of the message. We will then take steps to delete the child's information.

**5\. Protection of Personal Information**

We care about the security of your information and take steps to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to the information you provide to us. Although we have adopted reasonable measures to protect your personal information, no protection measure is 100% failure-proof. If you become aware of any technical vulnerability affecting LeEco Services or have any concerns, please email [Privacy-US@le.com](mailto:privacy-us@le.com).

**6\. Your Rights and Choices Regarding Information**

You may have certain rights regarding the information we maintain about you. If you choose to decline to share certain information with us, request the correction or deletion of some of the information we collect or withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide you with some of the features and functionality of the LeEco Services.

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your LeEco account. LeEco may be required to retain information we collect by law or may be permitted to retain it for legitimate business purposes even if you submit a request for correction or deletion. We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access, correction, or deletion is not required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made by contacting us at [Privacy-US@le.com](mailto:privacy-us@le.com).

You may disable the collection of exact location information from your device by changing the settings on your device, however, if you do not provide your exact location information, the LeEco Services may not function correctly or at all.

**7\. Third-Party Sites and Services**

LeEco Services may contain advertisements for and links to third-party websites, applications, products, or services, including through "plug-ins," widgets, buttons, and other third party features or integrations made available on and connected with LeEco Services. Our products and services may also use or offer products or services from third parties − for example, content and applications. Information collected by third parties on through their websites, applications, products, and services is governed by the privacy practices of those third parties. LeEco is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties, and this Privacy Policy does not govern the use or disclosure of any information you choose to disclose to third parties.

**8\. International Transfer and Access; Users from Outside the United States**

All information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. Information that we collect may be stored on your device or stored on our servers and transferred to, stored and processed in the United States or any other country where LeEco or its service providers maintain facilities, including jurisdictions that may not have data privacy laws that provide protections equivalent to those provided in your home country. By using the LeEco Services, you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**9\. Privacy Questions and Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or LeEco's collection, use, disclosure, transfer or storage of your information, or if you would like to notify us about a possible breach of security or local privacy laws, please contact us at [Privacy-US@le.com](mailto:privacy-us@le.com)

LeEco may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post notice of modifications to these terms on this page. You should look at these terms regularly. Changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective no sooner than fourteen (14) days after they are posted. Your continued use of LeEco Services after the posting of changes constitutes your acceptance of those updates.

**10\. Arbitration Agreement and Class Action Waiver.**

**IF YOU ARE A VISITOR OF OUR WEBSITES OR USER OF THE LEECO SERVICES AND SUBJECT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU AGREE THAT ALL DISPUTES AND CLAIMS BETWEEN YOU AND LEECO WILL BE SETTLED BY BINDING ARBITRATION INSTEAD OF IN COURTS OF GENERAL JURISDICTION AS PROVIDED IN OUR TERMS OF SERVICE LOCATED AT WWW.LEECO.COM/GENERALTERMS.**

**11\. Applicable Law and Venue**

By using any LeEco Service, you agree that the Federal Arbitration Act, applicable federal law, and the laws of the state of California, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern this Privacy Policy and any dispute of any kind that might arise between you and LeEco. In the event that this Section 11is severed in any legal action, then the parties agree that any legal relief sought will be brought in the federal or state courts serving Santa Clara County, California.

**12\. Survival**

If any provision or provisions of this Privacy Policy are held to be invalid, illegal, or unenforceable, the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions will remain in full force and effect.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy periodically to stay up-to-date about our privacy practices.
